[
    {
        "question": "speak",
        "answer": "spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "eat",
        "answer": "eaten"
    },
    {
        "question": "grow",
        "answer": "grown"
    },
    {
        "question": "make",
        "answer": "made"
    },
    {
        "question": "wear",
        "answer": "worn"
    },
    {
        "question": "drink",
        "answer": "drunk"
    },
    {
        "question": "do",
        "answer": "done"
    },
    {
        "question": "sell",
        "answer": "sold"
    },
    {
        "question": "know",
        "answer": "known"
    },
    {
        "question": "steal",
        "answer": "stolen"
    },
    {
        "question": "give",
        "answer": "given"
    },
    {
        "question": "write",
        "answer": "written"
    },
    {
        "question": "hold",
        "answer": "held"
    },
    {
        "question": "pay",
        "answer": "paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "teach",
        "answer": "taught"
    },
    {
        "question": "read",
        "answer": "read"
    },
    {
        "question": "sing",
        "answer": "sung"
    },
    {
        "question": "begin",
        "answer": "begun"
    },
    {
        "question": "bite",
        "answer": "bitten"
    },
    {
        "question": "break",
        "answer": "broken"
    },
    {
        "question": "bring",
        "answer": "brought"
    },
    {
        "question": "catch",
        "answer": "caught"
    },
    {
        "question": "choose",
        "answer": "chosen"
    },
    {
        "question": "freeze",
        "answer": "frozen"
    },
    {
        "question": "keep",
        "answer": "kept"
    },
    {
        "question": "ride",
        "answer": "ridden"
    },
    {
        "question": "see",
        "answer": "seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "show",
        "answer": "shown"
    },
    {
        "question": "take",
        "answer": "taken"
    },
    {
        "question": "put",
        "answer": "put"
    },
    {
        "question": "find",
        "answer": "found"
    }
]